and also i think we all know mrs is a
big full of elites especially from the
retail industry and this is the reason
why
you joined mrc i think one of the reason
you joined rca
expect to know each other expect to know
the retail tycoon i can see many here
and here we come ripping all of them
together
we bring you together sorry you can mix
around
if you don't do it i think the next
morning six o'clock
you can see joining women that is
a bni function a little more
okay now uh
our news president we're elected
president
with a deadline what's the deadline
our
um
we were told by the president that we
should get closer to remember
i get also a member or the new elected
houser
you see it's not it's not easy for mrsa
council
especially every time when we change the
new president now
we see very busy one you know this is
the first event after the new
uh new team um
you see this is the first event after
the new team was formed
and co get together we always want to do
it you know even before during during
the
three years time only thing after mca we
can't do anything
we can't do anything so we only today's
event
is we only limit to 70 bucks visit to
ceo only visit the ceo
and uh when we open i think one we can
be all
the seat taken up so can we give
yourself
word space is always like a movie step
long enough to come
long enough to cover the content
short enough to be sure you're not going
there long enough to be interesting
okay so
now before but last but not least
i want to convey a message from our
president
that's a lady okay she's
having her first charity
event that is love not just heart
for the young not young
or the singer mothers so
if you can this is the zero stress i
call it like basically
i would want to remember this what's
that
[Music]
she got all right
something like that so our campaign also
zero stress
okay helping this single
mother you can donate as low as 50
ringgit
or 50 000 it's up to you
[Music]
so she will give you more privilege i
thought today is an event that please
open your mind and weeks around
we happy happiness today okay enjoy
yourself happy new year thank you