[Music]
yes i was told to refer to this
sanitation list
let me know if i missed anything else
michelle mrca president
dr dr jennifer mrc advisor dr street
gary chua
mrca immediate vice president honorary
presidents
of mrca dr albert chem dr k sim kings
after 3 years singapore disney 2
president advisor dr lubin mrca
cu get together organizing care person
mrcax schools councils youth and members
ladies and gentlemen a very good
afternoon to all of you
ladies and gentlemen it's a real
pleasure and a privilege for me to stand
in front of you
i'm standing in front of thought leaders
visionaries industry captains
and leaders of your respective
industries and it just gives me a very
very
warm heart to welcome all of you so
please join me as we put our hands
together to welcome all of you
i was told to give a speech but i'm
standing in front of
you know ceos and then very very
experienced people so i shall not give a
speech
i don't have a script for you today but
what i'm going to do is to share with
you very candidly
and also learn from you along the way so
i want to give you some perspective last
year i traveled to 28 countries my fear
reminded me i traveled to 28 countries
ranging from southeast asia
north asia europe eastern europe western
europe
the united states canada and all the way
to the middle east and
africa as well and this was an amazing
experience whenever i go to different
countries
so when i go to indonesia the indonesian
suite is indonesia
you go to thailand they will tell you
[Music]
and if you go to hong kong
malaysian and very very proud to be
malaysian
and then when you go to china
[Music]
and of course in malaysia your home
country you speak
differently it's just so amazing to be
in malaysia
where you can connect to the rest of the
world with different cultures
and of course when i go to korea a lot
of people approach me and they say
i think i've seen you on some k-pop
channel
i'm just a simple malaysian just like
all of you and very very proud to be in
malaysia
and you know when we go to different
countries we also get to integrate and
learn from the different cultures
when i was in africa of you know some of
the people who brought me to africa
i was amazed to see that the evolution
in africa was pretty amazing
i saw people using cashless mobile
devices to transact
in the retail store when you go to china
you see people doing
all these things checking in through the
hotels everything to online channels
in germany and japan you see people
using robotic arms to
to do all the automation in factories
and if you think about what we've done
for silicon valley
a lot of the ideation in silicon valley
which can visit consistently
is actually not done in silicon valley
malaysians actually deliver a lot of
these products
but it's branded at silicon valley it's
branded as you know the united states is
branded as europe
but a lot of us in malaysia have amazing
talent
and this is what i wanted to share with
everyone today and hopefully just
have a little bit of a um you know
sharing session to share
some things that we've actually gone
through i'm not going to take too much
time
but what i thought is to give you a bit
of a perspective 200 years ago
90 percent of the world's population
worked in agriculture
that's 200 years ago today
about 2 percent of the world's
population works in agriculture
and when my staff told me today i
thought i could just sit down there with
all of you and just realize myself
they say it cannot because you've got to
stand on stage and give a speech but
i've got to work very hard for them just
as
they were very hard for the organization
but it's two percent of the world's
population work in agriculture today
why is that so because technology
advancement has actually led
to a lot of changes and today we don't
need so many human resources to work in
you know farms can anybody make a guess
what is this auto that you see on one
screen
okay maybe some of you say it's a super
computer it's super super computer
and this supercomputer was the first
machine that contributed in the landing
of apollo 11
in 1969. some of us were born during
that
some of us were not but in this group i
think
maybe we have seen her enough to be able
to know in 1969
you know this was a full meet-up now
this super computer
just to put things in the right
perspective was only
six megabytes improvement size
that is smaller than your pokemon app
that is 40 000 times smaller than your
iphone
your iphone has more processing power
and storage compared to this super
computer
that helped apollo 11 in 1969 land
can you imagine the advancements of
technology in your computer that's in
your pocket
has more processing power than this
super computer it can
text it can do messaging and voice you
can do internet processing it can be
e-commerce
it can do video and all of the things
that you want to do
and this is changing the way that we
work every day the current landscape is
extremely confusing
people talk about social media you can
see more than 243 000
photos uploaded you see 3.8 million
searches on google
these are just some examples you see a
million swipes you see netflix eighty
seven
thousand two hundred and ten thousand
these are of course estimates are not
exact numbers
but you get the point over the last 60
seconds although
millions millions of reports have been
generated
it's not like if we go and publish your
website the traffic will come naturally
it's not going to be the case
so this is extremely confusing and the
amount of data that the world is
throwing at is growing that
exponentially every minute every second
while we're eating when we're sleeping
or we're having lunch we're having
coffee data is
just growing because people are
searching for products online and this
is something that
we in malaysia have a great opportunity
to understand how this grows
radio took 38 years to reach 50 million
users tv to 13 years internet four years
ipod four years
and facebook took only nine months to
reach 100 million users
pretty amazing but also intimidating and
daunting and scary
if we do not realize that and of course
this room of learned people
don't have this problem but we know that
today we have about 7 billion
in terms of the world's population we
have close to 10 billion connected
device which is more than the population
of the entire world we by 2020 we would
have exceeded 100 billion connected
devices meaning to say
that each of us here don't only have one
connected device
you have a mobile phone you have a
connected tv you have a connected car
perhaps it connects to this to the
social media connects to
internet you probably have a connected
tablet as well
and many more connected and your
children also
and this is daunting but it's what's
happening so we have a very very
connected world a hyper connected with
tournament
with 10 billion connected network and
this is going to go 100 billion
over the next eight years so the rate at
which we're generating data is rapidly
outpacing our human capacity to cope
with it
and we need to be able to do things much
more efficiently
this is as usual as we say whether in
the retail space
can be just normal and it might be
simple
because this is what we do to get from a
to b we ride a bicycle this is just an
analogy
but if we think that's fine every day
we'll write already might still nothing
wrong
with it what happens if we find that our
competitors
can actually use this to get to the same
destination
faster better more efficient
and frankly speaking there is no reason
for other people not to use this
if they can go to the same destination
the global landscape is disorientating
there is an eruption of disruptive
technologies
meaning change that incumbents cannot
deal with
and because of the fact that there's a
lot of fluidity and uncertainty
businesses have to strategize today and
no one can assume that traditional basis
of competitive advantages
will remain things are changing the only
concept is change so we know about the
first and second and third revolution
the industrial revolution shows that
first initiative is all about steam
called second about mechanization and
third about you know electronics and
factories
and of course the fourth one which is
the most disruptive of them all
i think we heard our energetic mrca
president talk about ai talk about all
the things that we're doing with all the
good initiatives
ir 4.0 is going to have a massive change
and a massive impact in terms of how
we're doing business
and it doesn't just restrict one gear it
disrupts all
including retail so we are we're looking
at how
pins are changing now let's talk a
little bit about 90.
as we know forbidden numbers has
impacted almost everyone and this is how
maybe a busy street
used to be in perhaps tlcc in town world
and so and so forth
but after 2019 things are very different
pre post and after and this is not just
affecting one industry as we mentioned
we still have a lot of conferences with
people all across the world in fact
our office hours have been longer as you
would imagine
it's now 11 12 1 a.m 2 a.m people are
not so respectful of our time anymore
but we still understand
that they need to function saturday
sundays as well some of you might have
the same problems
i hope not but we have that problem that
people like
people are at home people are doing
things remotely
and this is not just in southeast asia
it's europe it's in america
it's everywhere and things are changing
very very rapidly
we work with many american brands many
european members many japanese friends
many korean brands many singaporeans
and face masks are becoming the new
normal
and of course face masks are also slowly
becoming the new fashion
and trend temperature taken everywhere
you go
and our new best friend and sanitizer
lots of things are changing as we speak
one thing i'd like to share and put
things in perspective in 1964
smp 500 companies 10 year
average lifespan 33 years and that was
how long this company would last before
it gets acquired
or whether it would disappear in 2016
this lifespan reduced to 24 years
in 2027 it is only 12 years
it is extremely intimidating this is
from mckinsey
and you will see that this information
is extremely
intimidating that means if companies
don't evolve
we are not going to be relevant so
that's something
so constant change is a new norm
one of the things that we've seen in
terms of the long-lasting profit 19 when
we talk to many of our customers
in and across the world that's prior
less current and this
and this future the new global consumer
research shows that consumers are
radically changing their lives in
response to economy
they are becoming more savvy they are
still buying
many consumers are facing new personal
situations what that means is that maybe
some of them
have lost their jobs some of them are
more conscious about hygiene factors
some of them don't want to go up too
much but they want to do the research
online
and consumers are shopping with greater
awareness of the environment
but there is a huge rise there's no
denial that there's huge rise in digital
commerce especially in low or new
low frequency customers might need to
continue prospering so you can see that
the sales
and and everything pre is is shaded in
gray and current in light purple
and of course the future so this is not
going to be something that disappears
that people come back
to the train they are so used to working
from home they are so used to
dealing with things online so this is
going to change very very rapidly
so one of the things that we probably
have to take a look at is how we disrupt
and reinvent our businesses
i've had the opportunity to meet up with
all these guys apart from
choice icon and all these guys amazing
people
jeff bezos jack ma kirby chen and karin
always is looking
of course richard branson
and the way they think is crazy out
there
the only other guy i haven't had a
chance to meet but i'll never have to
see is
steve jobs but the rest of the guys
they're all crazy guys
right and what they've done is they've
disrupted different types of businesses
um and just revolutionize how things
really happen
one thing that we should think about is
that if you think of holden
or gm toyota these are all good
brands but when you think of tesla
tesla is more valuable in all in
particular
how can the big health service have
enough sales tesla doesn't have enough
profits
it's just crazy but they have actually
innovated it to a state of your own
right of course you don't want to take
struck sometimes
but the innovation stuff is there and
hopefully infusion is also none of us do
that
how do we cope with the new world order
and new economic frontier we need to
think about how we
deal with the world with driverless cars
and maybe think about this
the car of tomorrow will become of the
horse will become the horse of the day
let me ponder for a moment that is a
wonderful moment to think about that
what is the horse of today
the horse of the day and the horse of
yesterday the horses yesterday was a
necessity
the horse of today is the laundry you
don't need a horse
the car of today is a necessity the car
tomorrow
maybe you don't need a car anymore maybe
there's a drivers car that takes you
around you don't need to park
so things are going to change very
rapidly and what we think today is the
norm
will result in a new norm very very
quickly that is what we discuss with
business leaders every day
they say that this is the problem i'm
facing can we say what do you think is
going to happen
in three months time six month time
three years i think it's gonna move
towards this is it is it true
let's think about it a bit more if you
think it's going to happen in six months
time
then do it now because when the month
number six arrives
and you try to do it like what happened
in kobe 19
you're right now we're going to go into
a digital transformation it's a little
bit too late because
because it's already happened so we need
to think of the next one but never too
late
if we are starting something early um
there are a lot of disruptors netflix
uber
amazon airbnb we can't blame them
because the market is
i'm doing this does anybody know who
this guy is
kevin costner
yeah second report right so one of the
famous things that senator paul said is
that people he had asked his customers
what they wanted
they would have told him that they
needed plaster forces
fortunately he didn't do faster horses
and he invented the automobiles and cars
and that's why we benefited from it
as you could see that horses were not
going to be the future
cars would be the future does anybody
know who this guy is
right so steve jobs is what did he say
he said that
customers normally ask him to give them
what they want but that's not his
approach
his job is to figure out what they're
going to do before they do it and to
read things they're not yet on the page
and that's something that we have to
discuss and i think malaysians have
great creativity
all of us leaders over here yourselves
we can brainstorm if we can do amazing
things
everything virtual assistants are going
to be the norm
in by 2022 85 of all customer
interactions will be handled without
accumulation
we're working with dbs we're working
with many banks we're working with
hotels and results to really do things
that can cope with our
human beings only human beings will be
escalated to make decisions but not the
money in jobs 24 hours
i'm going to skip through this but then
there's a big data are many identifying
new opportunities reliable
decision-making improved official and of
course new business opportunities
but the biggest biggest question when
you ask most people on the street not
people in this office not people in this
room
he said why do you think what are the
benefits of ai
and digital transformation if you go on
the street what is the biggest
answer that you get from most people
is they will tell you this they don't
know
and then it's scary because if we don't
and we're still if they don't admit that
they don't know it becomes a problem so
all of us might not know everything
but we need to know that the future is
here we need to think about what's going
to happen
and that is something that we're going
to work together champions and leaders
essentially those who understand that
there's difficult difference between
obstacles and opportunity
and to turn both into the advantage i
wanted to share just one simple network
with you
here's a simple story that we've heard
many times before
this story of the hair and the tortoise
and i thought it is very relevant in
this current era
so all of us know this story the hair
and the tortoise
the hair and the tortoise decided that
they wanted to have a race
and of course the hair being very quick
and speedy
so the tortoise of course will challenge
you to raise so the herring
tortoise started from the you know the
starting point
he had sped all the way to the nearby
when he reached me
it way what did he do he was complacent
he was lazy so he took a nap
and the tortoise saw the head taking a
nap and overtook the head
of course everybody knows that who won
the race
he was the oldest so behind the story
was that
slow and steady means the race because
his hair was complacent it was arrogant
and we thought that was the end of the
story i know it wasn't the end
and there was a second story that
the second race was that the hair and
the tortoise
the hair said that i'm so fast it cannot
be that i can lose to the 20 squeeze
also
so this time the hair challenged the
tortoise to a second race he said i will
challenge you again in the 26th don't
worry about this guy
he's going to slip it away anyway so
they started from the same point and
they had spat
yeah and of course the tortilla said
turmeric is going to sleep
but at this time the hair was not
complacent he was ironic he went all the
way to the finish line and he won the
race
so what is the moral of this story the
second story
slow and steady is great
it's good but fast and steady always
winslow and sticky hands
so the hair said you're slow and steady
i'm fast and steady
so fast it always wins so we thought
that that was the end
but the third story is that the tortoise
said that
this came very fast physically gifted
let me challenge the guy again
he invited her and said i'll challenge
you again follow
my terms i will decide the route to the
race so they started from the same point
but the tortoise said i will decide on
the finishing line
so the hair went all the way i'm not
going to sleep i'm not going to fall for
this trap so he went all the way
and he found out that on the map to hit
to the finishing line
it was a river the hair
started to scratch his head starting to
first fight he stopped at everybody he
said what am i going to do
can't do anything the tortoise slowly
came there so that
high or river it's okay why is so what
is the moral
behind the third song slow and steady is
good
the past activity is greater but if i
play to my strengths
i will always beat this guy so if you
are in the yangtze river
don't fight the crocodile if you're in
the pacific ocean don't fight the shark
if you're in malaysia don't play with
the guys say partner
if you find a fella who is six foot five
don't play basketball
honey you want to play a badminton okay
[Music]
so that was the third story and we
thought it was the end
so the fourth story is that their hand
thought this came together and said okay
let's challenge each other again
and this time they say that let's do it
differently you are very fast
i can do a lot of things and i can swim
past the river so they they decide on
the same route
and this time what happened was the hare
took the tortoise on his back
he ran from the start to the river very
fast
and when you arrive at the river which
they can't go any further
the hair then went onto the tortoise
back on his shelf and the tortoise
brought him
faster and then my friends
is the end of the story
is great if you paid your strengths
that's great if you can find a way
not to do everything yourself people as
partners in collaboration
that is
[Music]
so we all learn lessons if y'all learn
from each other
i just wanted to share that partnering
with us it doesn't mean that you might
be everyone
of course you have to find people to
give these friends and sometimes you
find really good partners some people
don't
but the way that we teach is going to
admit our kids jobs that's what
jack ma said i met up with him and he
was singing oprah
and he was sharing
he's a very good opera singer
stephen hopkins of course says that he's
a firm believer that humans are limited
by slow biological evolution
we can never ever complete and we can be
supported and supplemented with some
technology
some of you might have seen this before
if you have roughly writing yes your age
the matrix because many of us haven't
seen this again who the hell is
matrix okay no you don't care
if you see this once and zeros but you
can see it this way
then we can see the real opportunity
seeing between the lines
and that is something that is truly
amazing when sometimes we sit amongst
leaders and a spark
and the light bulb appears that we
suddenly find an inspiration that this
is going to change how the industry
works
so with that i just wanted to share one
last thing
some key takeaways and some suggestions
um i learned from
all the business leaders yourselves and
steven distinguished case all the time
what i do think that is important that
what i've learned is that
it's important to build skills and
capabilities either in-house or through
partners
sometimes we can do everything alone
i've spoken to so many leaders they say
okay i'm building hardware i also want
to learn how to build software i would
build software i also want to do
e-commerce i do e-commerce i want to do
digital marketing i do digital i'll do
manufacturing i do maintenance i do
construction i do control
and then you ask him oh we have
cafeteria
everything they want to do then
sometimes they think that can they
really do it well
and this is a problem today a best
manufacturer might not be a good
marketeer
the best marketing might not be a good
manufacturer so we have to understand
our trends and weaknesses
and there's always many ways to work
with different people building a partner
ecosystem is very good
experienced partners who have done it a
thousand times would probably have some
experience that they have to share
like future next if we wanted to have
food with a really bad box but we love
food
but we will get a good partner to
prepare the food and
if we have somebody who wants to do
hardware on buildings we will get
the right person to do it as well so
focus on operational efficiencies we
could wins and tangible roi is very
important because
sometimes a lot of people go to the boss
and say that we invest in this investor
but no roi no glad
of course the bosses or financials will
improve that and then we look at
adjacent industries by identifying
opportunity and potential threats
but one thing that's very important is
develop a flexible
agile solution treatment because things
will change along the way
be prepared for that change and be fast
identify the neglected unmind
opportunities with a clear roman overall
strategy
but most importantly the most important
thing is
do not wait whatever the decision is
do not wait think about it carefully
start small
think big with a vision and scale really
fast
because time waits for no man today we
build something
and when a crisis strikes we are ready
the companies that we've seen in kobe 19
period
that are able to stand up are those that
help that had a system
way
those who are not prepared wait for the
crisis to hit and try to do it
a little bit too late so we can always
prepare that but start now
um think big with a vision skill fast it
doesn't need to be a costly exercise
otherwise excuse me i would like to have
a spot on that to see that
we as fusion ex are very privileged to
have you as friends
all mrca folks friends you never
fantastic leadership team
you now have a lot of women power and
you have
that has made the path and foundation so
there's so much energy that i can see
fusionx hopefully is a friendly and
supportive partner we are happy to help
not just
in words in strength in spirit in effort
in kind and also in funding so it
doesn't what we can do for any other
things but i do hope that malaysia
with all of your leadership will be
successful and
we are very fortunate to see that you
know there are some companies are doing
well
and we are one of those that we think we
can support this because i think
it will be great for the country to have
increasingly funds so with that i wanted
to just say
that i want to thank you for everything
and the journey of the thousands
experience with us thank you so much i
hope you have a great
session today
[Music]
so if you have any questions you can
always uh approach letters three island
sorry um maybe during the
get together sessions