because he's the host for this gracious
event
so let's give him
jennifer much respected very very
successful business lady
if you need to know how to become you
know the top-notch
business entrepreneur go to her
my very capable dr sri gary choi i need
to say something that was doing
the past events that we have had were
grant and bake
but they were not bad at all they were
wonderful because
it was this event that put us at where
we are today i'm just actually helping
you to fill up the gaps
and
of the um dr albert chung dr j simkin
douglas street nelson court
and my very first president advisor dr
winston chu
of course the oc for this event
uh mrcs4 councils okay when i was
looking at the salutation listeners now
i found this
good youth so i was asking the secretary
stuff
who are the new fear any one of you here
is below 21.
i knew come on okay but so
i'm going to categorize those people who
are seated here as you
because for the ability of them to sit
this way they must be you isn't it
for actually hosting this wonderful
event
and a respected sea level mrcs member
i must say that with your mask on i
can't
actually recognize many of you but it's
good to see that your mask is off
we are observing the sop but it's fun
sometimes to be able to take off the
mask a little bit
we are getting here to basically hold
the first
uh ceo get together as how it was
explained by dr lewin
uh i wanted to call it the networking i
say no
networking is very serious he likes the
word
get together get together meaning you
can get together and party as well so
get together it shall be um i'd like to
take a little more
to just read out a little bit about
fusion next and i'm going to just follow
my script
because it's so important to say every
wonderful thing about what future next
has
attained today and i'm i'm going to just
say a bit is because if i'm going to
read everything what they have achieved
i will occupy the whole time for this
evening
so um yeah here it goes fusionnet has
actually grown from the ancient based
i.t
company so for its present status
it is actually the largest artificial
intelligence
recorded in short ai and data technology
company
not only for the region in fact has
helped a lot company to expand
globally fissionnet has also helped
many conglomerates and sme across the
world
to improve their businesses with human
nice and effective use of
technology i like the word technology
because
i remember when i was given the
opportunity to visit this wonderful
facility you know i asked that those
three ivan one question i'm not sure
whether he'll remember i say do you have
a post for me
i don't mind working here i'm not sure
whether you get a chance to tour today
but it's really
amazing my goodness i i wish you get the
facility
the opportunity to visit this place and
dr sri has actually led and been
involved in numerous initiatives
advanced technology
adoption and local businesses to drive
the advancement
in the tech and e-commerce industry this
has given
its clients the ability to compete and
successfully at
regional and global level fishernet was
also
honored with an outstanding achievers
award from the sme association
of malaysia and the platinum business
award
in 2018 i trust that
the industry ivan and your expert team
you will bring about
more advancement latest and more
impactful innovative to help all of us
congratulations for your key
achievements
okay now i can go free already okay um
the reason why we have decided to have
dco get together is because
we feel that we want to get to know you
better as i was saying just now all the
past events that mrca has helped
us for uh many very large scales
because of the pandemic situation we
can't do so
but we feel that we are missing you guys
every one of you
you know um uh how we want to come
together
is really for the purpose of fulfilling
my objectives uh
for my channel i have here my council
members i just
wish to just have them to stand up for
you guys to take a look at them do you
mind gentlemen and lady
for the counselor for 2020-2022
ladies and gentlemen i ask them to stand
up is because
if you need help go to them
if you don't do it right it's their
thoughts
you know i have a very wonderful thing
because it's not easy
um being a lady
they like to call me the first ever not
ever yeah the first lady president it's
not easy actually to hate such a big
organization that
all my past presidents have built you
know
from actually a 100 strong members our
membership has actually reached more
than 500 right now
but more importantly all of you are
actually
in amazingly successful businesses so
it's not easy to leave
you know an association of such kind so
my team and i
actually discussed uh that in this very
crucial time why not have something that
we can come together
and the reason why i want to do so is
actually very much in alignment with
the very first vision of the founder of
mrca
who knows the founder of mrca
is a very humble and very kind you know
you know that he's a founder for pro con
i had a wonderful opportunity to talk to
him several times and
i being a very inquisitive person by
nature i asked him
why did he form mrca he said that
you know something shelly if you want to
be successful in business
you need to join forces because when you
join forces you know everything becomes
easier do you do so here's my very
objective
of actually having this networking
session so that you can actually join
forces
learn from each other share your
knowledge and then we will actually
you know bring your business to another
level my second objective of course
is very much linked to me being a woman
okay being a woman i feel that
it is about time we get our fair share
of recognition
i know that there are wonderful
gentlemens who actually
recognize our achievements and
capabilities unfortunately
out there is not always the case so the
purpose of setting up the woman division
is to help lots of women to be given the
chance to show
you know their capabilities empower them
so that they can
help to build the nation as well so if
uh
women division was just formally formed
under the leadership of none other than
that of winnerling
dr william can you just say hi to
everyone
the timeline is empower the woman build
the nation
do you know something we have already
have so many women who are joining the
uh the woman division i hope the uh
ladies strong ladies of uh fisher next
will also join us
sorry dr okay
my third objective will be really to um
enlarge as well as make the f and b
industry an impactful one this is really
the vision of my very capable ipp 93
garage
during his tenure he is always saying
that you know we are not well
represented
for the fact that we have so many fmb uh
players you know
um you know we our voice is not hurt
and we call ourselves the de facto
leader with this
industry you can't do it we have to have
more people to join us
and he has personally volunteered to
chair
that division let's give a big round
uh dentistry is going to have his first
uh press conference uh
is it this month industry probably
twenty seconds yeah
so for those of you who are in uh fmb
please approach him
we need your help you know if you could
join us and then
whenever there are issues pertaining to
the fme industry we could then actually
form a very large coalition to be able
to have a larger representation
you know sometimes we don't need to
wrestle the arm of the government
but there are times we don't have a
choice no recording you know
okay all right okay my fifth and sixth
will be
the fifth one will be to really assist
in recovery
i feel that at this time right now lots
of us are
be suffering a little bit you know um i
was
having a chance to have a little bit of
dialogue with some of you you know y'all
were saying that uh
some of you have actually recently just
lifted listed your company
and then you are not really attaining
the desired result we want
i i hope that you'll be patient you know
while many of us
do not really see the light at the end
of the tunnel but i feel that if we
are all careful you know do our parts
this bad time will go
and the important thing is we all have
to stay very positive motivated
because we can't let this virus take us
you know but at the same time we're very
careful i read a very interesting
article it seems that we are no longer
having any interest in the virus
but trust me the virus has a lot lots of
interest in us
so let's let's be very careful okay and
my my sixth one will be to set up a
continuing information
hub for the members i know that in the
past you know we may be lacking in terms
of communicating with you guys
you know um sorry we are going to do
better we're going to have
you know the secretary as well as the
council members to work closer together
collectively so that whenever we receive
any pertinent information
we will come to you and let you know but
i hope you come to us first because
sometimes we may be missing you out
if you have any questions you know or do
come to us we'll try our level best to
help you
we would have a lot of uh very
influential people here they're all at
the front row
they can help you ah that is free
kicking
so and of course my advisor you know
my past president as well as uh jen you
know
i'm sure if you have any pertinent
issues that you need advice
it will be actually willing to you know
lend a helping hand
now um i come to this part about my pet
project which is a single mother project
can i have some slime
oh my photo is really nice though
okay so about this uh project why i
actually started this project is because
um
it's very sad to read the newspaper
articles every day do you know that
the people who are badly affected in
fact
the most adversely affected are the
single mothers
i i was reading just not long ago
to be precise it was on 25th of august
it was actually a report by this family
on the age in short it's called f.o.e
it was stated that for this you know
whole
pandemic 30 overs and close to 40
percent of the people who are losing
their jobs
a single mother and well still
fifty percent of them have no money of
access to social protection
at all i and the secretary team plus my
committee members visited a lot of
homes you know it was very
heartbreaking you know to see a lot of
single mothers
not only they have to care for their
families
they are basically the only bread winner
for their families as well
so that's how my deputy dr lubin
rightfully put it
it doesn't take us a lot he said 50 no
50 ringgitler minimum 100 okay
we don't actually ask a huge amount of
donation but of course if you are able
to give a little bit more it will be
wonderful
let's do our little part i feel that if
we can take from the society we can give
back to the society as well
lots of single mothers right now need
our help uh
thus far i uh we started the project on
14 august we are going to end it
on the 30th uh september my charity hey
jordan and his team are here they're
working really hard
you know to get a donation to meet our
target of one hundred thousand
um i'm glad to say that we are halfway
there fifty thousand we still have
another fifty thousand to me
but trust me the money will be carefully
managed meticulously distributed to the
right
organization whom we believe you know
the single mothers whom we have will be
able to sustain
and then learn to survive on their own
so hopefully you can take out the qr
code later
and then start to donate to this very
charitable tribe
my foundation chairman is here
with his very noble action he raised 1
million when he
started this project about 2010
i asked the secretary office to check
how much donation we have done so far
it's actually one million as well so i
think we should give ourselves a big
hand
okay the purpose of the co get together
once again you know it's very
interesting that i was told just now
that we are supposed to
go for breakout sessions and in the
breakout sessions you will each have
your own little party
so mine is um
[Music]
i don't know what
um
[Music]
and i feel that this difficult time
right now what had been
you know abnormal in the past has to
become part of our life and become
normal
so if we don't know how to you know do
this robotic kind of
um artificial intelligence we have to
all learn from them
so take the advantage advantage to learn
as much from them as possible
so i'm going to sign off here if you
remember
my tagline powered by you research
better powered by you means you will be
all the members
we will be all the council members thank
you very much and have a wonderful
evening